<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Malcolm Herbert on OpenEssence</title>
    <link>https://openessence.github.io/author/malcolm-herbert/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Malcolm Herbert on OpenEssence</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 13:20:21 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://openessence.github.io/author/malcolm-herbert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Decision Framework</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/opendecisionframework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 13:20:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/opendecisionframework/</guid>
      <description>What is the Open Decision Framework ? For the past few years Red Hat, have been grappling with the challenges of growing an open organization and sustaining our culture along the way. One tool we’ve been developing and testing is the Open Decision Framework, a collection of best practices for applying open source principles to business projects and decisions.
The Open Decision Framework contains the collective wisdom of an organisations staff, compiled into a flexible framework that helps decision makers and leaders seek out diverse perspectives and collaborate across teams and geos, to make better decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prep Call</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/prep-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 11:11:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/prep-call/</guid>
      <description>License Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/ What is a Prep Call (or Preparation Call)? Prior to any onsite or face to face meeting, a preparation call looks to provide an initial introduction to the project and identify an opportunity and an initial view of the stakeholders. This should be with all parties that are to be involved with the event, internal and customer / external.
 Run 30-60 minute conference call with customer, going through the Workshop Preparation Guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maturity Model</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/maturity-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 15:56:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/maturity-model/</guid>
      <description>Author Malcolm Herbert, Red Hat 2016
License Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/ What is a Maturity Model ? A Maturity Model can be used to describe a whole host of technology based environments. Rather than focusing on a specific software product they will look at - technology - process - people
For example, a Maturity model can be used to assess current System Management / Data Centre Management and is a useful tool to determine the current position of an organisation, especially in relation to Standard Operating Environment (SOE) and the related areas of Unix to Linux migrations or Continuous Delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engagement Client Preparation Doc</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/engagement-client-preparation-doc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 14:42:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/engagement-client-preparation-doc/</guid>
      <description>What is a Client Preparation Document It&amp;rsquo;s a document that maps out the prerequisites for a Discovery Session or other presales workshop. It ensures that all the key elements needed are actually in place prior to the meeting taking place.
The Document should be sourced around a particular theme, then edited to reflect customer details and passed on to the customer. It should outline a framework agenda for discussion and finalisation in the Pre-Call as well as potential outcomes from the one day Discovery Session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Delivery</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/agile-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 11:18:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/agile-delivery/</guid>
      <description>Author Malcolm Herbert June 2018
License Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/ What is Agile Delivery ? Agile delivery is an approach for delivering consulting or presales projects, based on the Agile methodology. It involves a range of Agile activities and approaches and the style of delivery varies significantly.
http://agilemanifesto.org/
Why use it? Because it&amp;rsquo;s Agile ? If you are a practioner and live Agile then this is the approach for you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>