<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Community on OpenEssence</title>
    <link>https://openessence.github.io/categories/community/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Community on OpenEssence</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 15:51:15 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://openessence.github.io/categories/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovery Session Report</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/discover-session-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 15:51:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/discover-session-report/</guid>
      <description>What is a Discovery Session Report ? Short report template for Discovery Sessions. The problem with some discovery sessions is that the documentation takes too long to produce and can be too extensive. Using templates ensures a succinct, easy to read report with the key findings.
A Discovery Session usually last for 1 day or less and the report should be written with this in mind; it should be short, concise and relevant to the workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Decision Framework</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/opendecisionframework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 13:20:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/opendecisionframework/</guid>
      <description>What is the Open Decision Framework ? For the past few years Red Hat, have been grappling with the challenges of growing an open organization and sustaining our culture along the way. One tool we’ve been developing and testing is the Open Decision Framework, a collection of best practices for applying open source principles to business projects and decisions.
The Open Decision Framework contains the collective wisdom of an organisations staff, compiled into a flexible framework that helps decision makers and leaders seek out diverse perspectives and collaborate across teams and geos, to make better decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Priority Exercise</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/business-priority-exercise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 12:06:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/business-priority-exercise/</guid>
      <description>What is a Business Priority Exercise? The business priroity exercise is a method for structuring a conversation with a customer around their strategy and business priorities.
Using 12 magnetic cards which contain generic priorities, the facilitator asks the group to select their top 3 from a business perspective.
As the group are working out which 3 to select, the facilitator should be asking probing questions about their thought process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maturity Model</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/maturity-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 15:56:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/maturity-model/</guid>
      <description>What is a Maturity Model ? A Maturity Model can be used to describe a whole host of technology based environments. Rather than focusing on a specific software product they will look at
 Technology Process People  For example, a Maturity model can be used to assess current System Management / Data Centre Management and is a useful tool to determine the current position of an organisation, especially in relation to Standard Operating Environment (SOE) and the related areas of Unix to Linux migrations or Continuous Delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure Architecture Workshop</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/infrastructure-architecture-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 11:39:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/infrastructure-architecture-workshop/</guid>
      <description>What is an Infrastructure Architecture Workshop? This is an activity which is designed to elicit requirements and propose an architecture for an infrastructure-type engagement. The outputs from the workshop are:
 A list of requirements A High Level Design document A Low Level Design document A task backlog  The outputs can then be fed to an implementation team who should be able to implement a solution that meets the requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Strategy Workshop</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/business-strategy-engagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 10:39:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/business-strategy-engagement/</guid>
      <description>What is a Business Strategy Engagement? The Red Hat Strategy Engagement takes business leaders out of their day to day environment to explore their future business strategy and position Red Hat as technology partner of choice.
The outputs from the workshops are:
Day 1
 Understanding of what a Journey Map is Agreed topics to take into the Journey Mapping Workshop Output document containing:  Customer Strategy Business Priority Output RTI Assessment document   Day 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Context Switching</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/context-switching-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 10:39:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/context-switching-workshop/</guid>
      <description>What is Context Switching? Context Switching can be described as multi-tasking which is often seen as a good thing. Unfortunately, we are not able to generate the same amount of output/value when we multi-task.
Much recent neuroscience research tells us that the brain doesn’t really do tasks simultaneously, as we thought (hoped) it might. In fact, we just switch tasks quickly. Each time we move from hearing music to writing a text or talking to someone, there is a stop/start process that goes on in the brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Thinking</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/design-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 12:39:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/design-thinking/</guid>
      <description>What is Design Thinking? Design Thinking was originally developed as a process for creative designers but has wider business and social applications.
Why use it? It is a positive, creative approach for the initial parts of solution development. It is a good way of getting fresh, new ideas into an existing organisation. Thinking outside of the box is one way of describing it.
Related Practices It can be used as part of a Discovery Session or as part of a wider development project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/pathfinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 12:39:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/pathfinder/</guid>
      <description>What is Pathfinder? Pathfinder is a web based application assessment tool which is used by customers to determine which applications could be containerised, the effort involved and any impediments to the containerisation process.
Pathfinder enables customers to view the order in which applications should be migrated as well as help determine the type of work involved e.g migrate, modernise etc, and a course estimate of the effort required.
Why use it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Preparation Call</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/workshoppreperationcall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/workshoppreperationcall/</guid>
      <description>What is a Workshop Preparation Call? This is an activity that is designed as a precursor to an Architectural Workshop, such as the Infrastructure Architecture Workshop. The outputs from the call are:
 A list of identified stakeholders and their areas of interest An agenda of workshops, with each workshop identified by subject matter and attendees  Why use it? The workshop preparation call should be used to set the agenda and scope of one or more workshops.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>