<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshop on OpenEssence</title>
    <link>https://openessence.github.io/tags/workshop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshop on OpenEssence</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 11:39:01 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://openessence.github.io/tags/workshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure Architecture Workshop</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/infrastructure-architecture-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 11:39:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/infrastructure-architecture-workshop/</guid>
      <description>What is an Infrastructure Architecture Workshop? This is an activity which is designed to elicit requirements and propose architecture for an infrastructure-type engagement. The outputs from the workshop are:
 A list of requirements A High Level Design document A Low Level Design document A task backlog  The outputs can then be fed to an implementation team who should be able to implement a solution that meets the requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Switching</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/context-switching-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 10:39:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/context-switching-workshop/</guid>
      <description>What is Content Switching? Context Switching can be described as multi-tasking which is often seen as a good thing. Unfortunately, we are not able to generate the same amount of output/value when we multi-task.
Much recent neuroscience research tells us that the brain doesn’t really do tasks simultaneously, as we thought (hoped) it might. In fact, we just switch tasks quickly. Each time we move from hearing music to writing a text or talking to someone, there is a stop/start process that goes on in the brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Model</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/schneider-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 16:39:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/schneider-model/</guid>
      <description>What is the Schneider Model? The Schneider cultural model isn&amp;rsquo;t a new approach (it has its origins in the mid 90&amp;rsquo;s) but it&amp;rsquo;s relevant today. When applying technical and process changes as part of a transformation, this activity provides the means of assessing the current culture and how effective these changes may be.
The Schneider Model identifies the primary, underlying culture which shapes the organisation. There are 4 main types: - Control - Cultivation - Collaboration - Competence</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Thinking</title>
      <link>https://openessence.github.io/practices/design-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 12:39:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openessence.github.io/practices/design-thinking/</guid>
      <description>What is Design Thinking? Design Thinking was originally developed as a process for creative designers but has wider business and social applications.
Why use it? It is a positive, creative approach for the initial parts of solution development. It is a good way of getting fresh, new ideas into an existing organisation. Thinking outside of the box is one way of describing it.
Related Practices It can be used as part of a Discovery Session or as part of a wider development project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>